AYINDE OLADIMEJI

REACT DEVELOPER

I have over 5 years of experience as a Mobile Engineer in designing & developing beautiful User Interfaces for applications, integrating with various databases, client-server applications with ReactJs framework. I adopt to highly collaborative work environment, finding solutions to problems and determining customer satisfactions. I have designed series of mobile applications across multiple APIs, third party integrations and databases. Passionate and hardworking with penchant for developing customized interface that factor in unique demands for accessibility, reachability and security



+2349030933281



<u>azeezoladimeji23@gmail.com</u>

RELEVANT SKILLS

- Reactis
- Firebase
- Tailwind CSS
- Tailwind UI
- Bootstrap
- Flexboss
- Grid
- JavaScript

WORK EXPERIENCE

React Developer (Doteightplus inc)

July 2017 - August 2020

- Collaborated in architecture, design and development of innovative projects.
- Maintain technical documentation, adhering to coding guidelines.
- Write code for database-driven application.
- Resolved system test and validation problems to provide normal program functioning.
- Fixed bugs and maintained application codebase

React Developer (Jelv inc)

September 2020 – March 2021

- Follow the latest concept and best coding practices for mobile apps.
- Maintain technical documentation, adhering to coding guidelines.
- Tested mobile application services to ensure there are no design or implantation flaws.
- Resolved system test and validation problems to provide normal program functioning

React Developer (Akromax inc)

December 2021 - june 2022

• Successfully re-design an app for over 2 million users. • Maintain technical documentation, adhering to coding guidelines. • Tested mobile application services to ensure there are no design or implantation flaws. • Resolved system test and validation problems to provide normal program functioning.

EDUCATIONS



BA in Mechatronic Engineering

Federal University of OYE EKITI Year of Graduation: 2018